# Z. Md Sharuf Raj

#### **DevOps Engineer**

**Phone:** +91 7305891418 / 9789933192 **Email:** thaiubasharuf@gmail.com

Address: Chennai, India

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/sharuf-md-81377230b

Summary: DevOps Engineer with the Course Knowledge Of DevOps completed from GUVI Institute, Chennai (September 2023 - March 2024) Looking for a Job in the DevOps Domain.

I have a 9 years of Experience in the field of Mechanical Engineering.

#### **SKILLS**

AWS | Linux | GitHub | Bash Scripting | Docker | Jenkins | CI/CD Pipeline | Terraform | Kubernetes | Prometheus & Grafana

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY	
Sales Associate   Electrolux Ltd.	Aug 2023 - Jan 2024
Sales Associate, August, 2022   Jio Infocomm, Chennai, India.	Jan 2023 - Jun 2023
Sales Associate   Reliance Digital, Chennai, India.	Sep 2021 - Dec 2022
MEP Site Engineer   GMP Technical Services LLC, Dubai, U.A.E.	Nov 2019 - Jun 2021
MEP Site Engineer   Awal Al Ghaith Elect. & Sanit. L.L.C, Sharjah, U.A.E.	Apr 2017 - Nov 2019
HVAC Engineer   AIRSYS PVT.LTD, Chennai, India.	Jun 2012 - Mar 2017

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Of Engineering Degree in Mechanical | Anna University, Trichirapalli

Apr 2011

## **WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS**

Linkedin | Github

#### **COURSES**

DevOps at GUVI GEEK Institute, Chennai PG Diploma in HVAC at Dimensional Acamedy, Chennai Sep 2023 - Mar 2024 Mar 2015 - Jun 2015 Jun 2024 - Jun 2024

## **PROJECTS**

DevOps Application Deployment | GUVI GEEK Institute, Chennai, Chennai

Mar 2024 - Apr 2024

DevOps Application Deployment is the Capstone Project Given by GUVI GEEK Institute, Chennai as my Final project for the DevOps Course and i have <u>Scored 7 out of 10.</u>

## **LANGUAGES**

English | Hindi | Tamil

www.resumod.co Created with ☐**RESUMOD**